Don't smile.
Will you leave me in the end even if you smile at me now?
When you get what you want,
You're going to leave me.
You said I'll do whatever you ask me to do,
Until you tell me to leave,
I'll stay with you.
I knew you were preparing for the recipe contest.
This tastes good.
How do you know that?
Did you think I'd rely on you
without knowing about you?
What?
Wait here for Kwang Soo,
okay?
What's going on?
The board decided to sell it.
When the financial team comes up with a price,
they'll sell it right away.
If we take out a loan using our restaurant chain,
we won't have to sell it.
To get the amount of money we need, Hannamdong Lady is our only hope.
I can't sell it while my father's away.
He has the final say.
I'll make an appointment,
but don't expect too much of it,
Everybody wants their share.
Don't you want the K Corporation?
My father abandoned his wife and children for the sake of money,
I watched my brother growing up.
I'm good for now.
Mr. Jo Min Hyuk was here.
You don't look happy.
No.
I actually dealt him a big blow.
But it doesn't make me feel better.
You heard about the decision?
If Min Hyuk can't keep the restaurant chain,
it'll be harder for him.
Well, as far as I'm concerned, it's not that hard for him.
He's still clinging to what he has,
so he must be okay.
Yoo Jung! Have a seat.
Yoo Jung, it's autumn.
You need to take care of your skin.
You're not 20 anymore.
Look at you. Your lips are all chapped.
You need to be ready for a new relationship.
Yoo Jung,
I spent a month's rent on this.
I'll give it to you.
Yoo Jung, you should know that I'm nice to you.
If you have that much money,
pay your rent.
Yoo Jung, how far did you go with Mr. Jo?
Have you kissed each other?
Hae Ri! Stop!
I think you did.
I have to go.
That's great.
Rent!
Three, four!
An ordinary happy birthday song
doesn't suit your special day.
So, we made a special birthday song for you.
It's a happy day. It's a joyful day.
The world is beautiful.
We're happy and joyful to celebrate
your birthday.
Sir.
What?
Happy birthday!
No present?
Sorry.
- Go bring Yoo Jung in. - Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
You chose it, you'll do the presentation.
Excuse me?
Have you finished the sauce?
Yes.
We'll meet the investor tomorrow.
We need to raise the value of our restaurant.
Write your recipe down and prepare a plan.
Sir,
That's beyond my ability.
How can you revenge while making food in the kitchen?
Don't think that I'll help you for no reason.
Ahn Do Hoon,
he is trying to sell the restaurant.
You jsut need to stop him
and I'll keep what's mine.
It's a win-win situation, okay?
What is it?
The Security Room called.
The footage has been recovered.
How did it go?
You're here.
I didn't know you'd be down here so quickly.
I was going to watch something fun.
Let's watch it together.
Kwang Soo! Let's start.
Kwang Soo remembered that he went to the cafe on that night.
Did you call me to show me this?
What?
It's not fun for you because you 've already seen it?
Yes.
I was with Yoo Jung on that night.
So,
I can guess what you're looking for.
But the place in the video isn't the scene of the accident.
This can't prove anything.
Excuse me.
If this can't prove anything...
Why did you find it so desperately
and even delete it?
Why?
It's him!
That bastard was driving on that night.
Kang Yoo Jung!
You idiot!
Like Ahn Do Hoon said,
the black box footage can't prove anything.
Make it work!
Let's go to the prosecutor's office.
Steak and pasta.
Here's your dish.
Enjoy!
Let's talk.
What's got you so afraid that you'd come here?
Did you tell him?
Did you tell Min Hyuk that I was driving?
I'm not that stupid.
It's you who make me terrible,
I'm the one who's suffering from your noble sacrifice.
I'm working.
If you want to talk to me, wait until I'm done working.
The prosecutor and the defendant were lovers.
And the prosecutor was Ahn Do Hoon.
So what?
Is that it?
Doesn't the case have to be tried again?
If there were a conflict of interest due to a personal relationship,
we would change a prosecutor.
However, he made a justice prosecution,
there's nothing illegal about that.
The defendant can file a complaint,
but that isn't the case.
If the defendant wasn't the real killer,
could we ask for a retrial?
What are you talking about?
That would shake the entire prosecution system.
Without solid evidence, it's not going to happen.
What?
Do you have solid evidence?
If I did,
would you take this case?
Who is the real?
Are you saying
Do Hoon did it?
Do you have any other evidence?
Did you hide something to use against me?
Yes,
Look at you,
I really wish I had hid something.
You can't break me down with that accident.
I'm not that mean.
I'm not like you.
Why?
Are you afraid of losing too much?
Enjoy what you have now.
I'll drag you down to the bottom myself.
Enjoy it while you can.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Bye.
Yoo Jung, this is your workplace.
If you want to chat with men during work hours,
you should resign.
Don't think that you can do everything you want because Mr. Jo cares about you.
Sorry! It won't happen again.
Who was that?
Mr. Ahn came to see me.
What for?
It's a personal thing.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I won't, if you tell me not to.
If you told me that you weren't driving on that day...
And Do Hoon was the one who was driving...
You won't be entangled with me.
No.
Even if...
Even if I hadn't been driving,
I was there with him.
On the night that she passed away,
I was definitely there.
It's natural for you to be angry with me.
What you ask me to do isn't tired at all,
But...
I'm afraid I might forget about it
and live as if nothing happened.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Sorry! The subscriber you dialed can not be connected for the moment...
Set another date.
Next time... Call me after Min Hyuk gets here.
Do it as if I were the customer.
Start.
Start right now.
It's a happy day. It's a joyful day.
The world is beautiful.
Do it again! Do it again!
Is this how you do it for our customers?
You should smile sincerely.
You can also dance.
I saw you did a good job earlier.
Look at me.
It's a happy day. It's a joyful day.
Start.
Come on.
What are you doing?
It's a happy day. It's a joyful day.
- The world is beautiful. - Louder.
- Louder. - We're happy and joyful to celebrate...
Your birthday...
Happy birthday!
That's how you spend your birthday.
I didn't want to bother you,
but I had to do my duty.
Happy birthday!
I'm sorry, something just happened.
Something?
Do you mean this?
It's so like you.
Is it his birthday today?
Yes.
What?
It is my birthday today.
Why didn't you ask her about the accident?
Don't you think she has the answer that you want to hear?
She won't tell me. Kang Yoo Jung.
The most solid evidence
I should hear from Ahn Do Hoon.
The lady that Min Hyuk is going to meet
tomorrow is more important than the board.
Is that why Mr. Jo changed his schedule for tomorrow?
If she decides to invest,
the board will side with Min Hyuk
rather than going through the complicated selling process.
That's a large sum of money.
That's why Min Hyuk is going to her in person.
All the contracts signed outside of the company have to go through the Legal Team.
I'll check the contract in person.
Yoo Jung will accompany Min Hyuk tomorrow.
I'll expect your performance tomorrow.
Even if
I wasn't driving,
I was there with him.
Idiot.
Even if Yoo Jung wasn't driving, what would you do?
I don't know how to bow and scrape to others.
I've never done it before.
I'm counting on you.
Come on in.
Hello.
I'm really appreciate that
your Legal Team came first to tell me about the investment condition in detail.
Really?
Have a seat.
This is our proposal.
You have a talented employee.
Mr. Ahn has offered me a good plan.
You've been investing a lot of money with the K Corporation.
I thought you should look through the information we have first
before you make a decision.
Why should I invest in King's Restaurant?
I can't just give you this money simply because I know you.
Can I use your kitchen?
Go ahead.
I didn't prepare a main dish on purpose.
I have confidence that our sauce
will go well with any dish.
My father owned a bakery for a long time.
I'm so fond of sweet food,
so he made buns with vegetables.
He mixed those vegetables that I didn't like with the sauce.
Even though he passed away.
The taste still lingers in my memory.
When you think of King's Restaurant,
the lingering taste is our value.
This is not Ms. Kang's private business.
Sell your personal nostalgia somewhere else.
I'm not here to sell my personal nostalgia.
I'm confident
that our new sauce will appeal to the taste buds of our customers.
Being confidnet isn't enough.
As the biggest shareholder, the King Hotel...
I'm the owner of the restaurant.
I thought you were here as a consultant on this deal.
I'm not here to represent the restaurant, I'm representing the K Corporation.
The taste do linger in my mouth,
You're working for the K Corporation, but you don't trust each other.
Yet, you want my money.
It's unreasonable.
The rumors that President Jo is seriously ill must be true.
What a disharmonious team.
Someone from the Shinhwa Hotel is here.
I have another appointment.
I'll think about it and get back to you.
Mr. Ahn.
You make me angry playing dirty like this.
I just did what the board asked me to do.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
Is that so?
Hang in there.
Until I go back.
Let's go.
Thank you.
For making me more disappointed in you.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
But because of me...
It's not your fault.
Nothing's been decided.
But...
Stop!
Can't you blame others?
It's easy.
If something goes wrong, blame Ahn Do Hoon.
What's this?
For your birthday.
It's a cream bun.
I don't have an oven, so I used a steamer.
It doesn't look good, but it tastes good.
I don't like sweet stuff.
Right.
Do you want to have dinner, then?
Take care.
I'll take it since you made it for me.
Unbelievable!
Long time no see.
You look even more handsome.
Who is that stand behind you?
One plus one.
Sandra,
has anything good happened?
I started a new business.
It's magical.
It tastes delicious.
Take a few drops.
It'll help with your immune system, blood circulation and increase your stamina.
You sell it for 20000KRW while buy it for 1000KRW.
We'll get arrested again.
Stop! If you take it,
you can get rid of the fat around your stomach as well.
Would you like to be my partner in this miraculous business?
Sandra.
It was his birthday today, I want to treat him to a dinner.
His birthday?
Really?
We should celebrate it.
Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you!
Our dear Mr. Jo.
Happy birthday to you.
Why don't you join us for dinner?
Have a seat.
Kwang Soo, eat with us.
Don't just stand there. Come and have a seat.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Have a seat.
Drink it.
Wow,
a new face! Welcome!
What's your name? What's your phone number?
I'm Choi Kwang Soo.
Choi Kwang Soo. I like that name.
Try it.
It's delicious.
Have a drink.
Go ahead. Drink up.
It's okay. I'll call a designated driver.
Drink as you wish.
You won't sleep at night.
Don't give him too much at once.
Let's sing a song.
Kwang Soo, sing a song.
Sing! Sing! If you can't sing, you can't get married.
Poor guy.
If you don't sing, we'll make you.
One! Hey! Two! Hey!
Three! Go! One, two! One, two, three, four!
When are you going to start?
My love for you is unconditional.
Unconditional, unconditional.
My love for you
is incomparable.
It's me.
My father. Is he in the operating room?
You can't meet her without an appointment.
Could you please
take this to her?
I made it last week, and it tastes perfect now.
Please.
Sir,
I found Ms. Lee Hye Jin.
Who?
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung's cellmate.
Why did she report Yoo Jung?
After she made a report to the police, Ahn Do Hoon wrote a letter of recommendation for her.
- she was transferred to a job training center. - What?
This is the surveillance camera footage that Ms. Lee Ja Yeong requested.
Please forgive me this once.
I can't let my father go just like that.
They found my father.
- Where is he? - Pohang.
Dad. Dad.
Dad. Dad...
I want to stay with you.
Is this because of Do Hoon?
Ahn Do Hoon.
That was Hannamdong Lady. Min Hyuk went to see her again.
She was wondering who Kang Yoo Jung was.
I guess she did well.
I didn't think she'd invest money for sentimental reasons.
We don't know that.
She's not curious about who you are though.
Would you like to have one?
- Are you determined to do this? - Why? Do you want to stop me?
What's our relationship?
Are you in a deeper relationship with Jo Min Hyuk than you are with me?
Do you want me?
Then separate her from Min Hyuk.
Can you do that for me?
If I do that, will you be with me?
What should I do?
I have to get married with him.
Would you be happy as my lover?
Both of us are silly. Right?
You don't need to stay up like that.
This isn't about business.
If this isn't about business, I wouldn't be here.
I have work to do.
I'll be brief then.
Lee Hye Jin. She reported Yoo Jung for child maltreatment.
Cellmate, right?
Why did you write a recommendation for her?
It has nothing to do with you.
It has nothing to do with me,
but it has something to do with Yoo Jung.
She used to try hard to protect you at all costs,
why has she turned her back on you. I'm really curious about that.
There is no secret in this world, right?
What is it that you want to say?
A prosecutor, who advocated justice,
took his own son away.
I told you that you and I weren't different.
I want to take back my words.
I'm not as vicious as you.
Is this why Yoo Jung left you?
Or do you have more secrets I don't know about?
Preventing her parole was your idea.
- Don't blame me, it's you who made the choice. - Jo Min Hyuk!
You're the one who stamped "denied" on the paper, not me.
I just wanted her to stay in jail
just like you wish.
But I'm regreting about that now.
Even before her parole was denied,
it was already decided
that she wouldn't qualify for parole.
That's why we deny her parole.
Did you feel it bothers you?
You're afraid that others will know what you did,
so you hired someone to make the parole itself impossible.
Take him.
San. He's not recovered yet.
Where are you taking San?
San! San!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
It's too mean.
Yoo Jung is so poor.
How can you judge me like that?
Both you and me didn't protect our woman.
Ji Hee!
Good! That's what I wanted to see.
Revealing your secrets one by one will be me more fun that way.
What happened to Yoo Jung's father... I'll look into it later.
I didn't know you were coming.
Your apartment is good,
but it must be boring.
You don't look good.
What's going on?
- Nothing. Where's mom? - She said she had an appointment,
and didn't come to the restaurant for a whole day.
Don't worry about us.
She said we should move,
but I talked her out of it.
Since you left, this place feels empty.
We don't need a big place.
It's old, and the slope is hard for you.
Move to a comfortable place.
I don't have to listen to the gossips outside,
and run my own restaurant,
I don't want anything more.
What?
Father. I'm doing good, right?
Why is the door open?
Oops! You scared me!
Why are you scared of your son?
No!
You should've called.
You're the one who hasn't called and have been gone all day. Where did you go?
Well... I...
Nothing...
I'll get changed first.
Okay.
What's wrong with her?
Have you eaten? I'll prepare some food for you.
What's wrong with her today?
She is in such a panic.
Hello. We're from King's Restaurant.
Hello.
I asked for you.
I haven't had a chance to held a birthday party for Min Hyuk.
I have to held one for him now.
Yes.
Set the table up over there. You can cook over there.
One's enough. You can go.
Is that okay?
Yes? Sure.
Min Hyuk! Min Hyuk!
Your father was sent into the recovery room yesterday.
How is he?
It's too soon to tell, but he should be fine.
He'll attend a meeting in Berlin before he comes back.
It'll be a good opportunity to show people that he's okay.
I heard about the investment. Good job.
She asked me about the girl you were with.
Is she the one you told me about before?
I know what I'm doing.
Your personal life is not my concern,
but I think you should be aware that
if anything affects your marriage with Se Yeon, it would lead to a terrible consequence.
Why aren't you handing Ahn Do Hoon's file over?
He cleaned up your mess.
Other than trying to control the board,
he's a good asset to our group.
We still have a use for him.
I'm more worried about Se Yeon.
Mr. Ahn and Se Yeon.
Keep an eye on them.
Min Hyuk's running late.
Min Hyuk, happy birthday!
What?
I never thought you'd settle for one woman.
Se Yeon sure is something.
Happy birthday, Min Hyuk!
I didn't have a chance to wish you a happy birthday.
Would you like a drink?
Can you bring us some wine?
What are you doing here?
What's this? What do you want?
I told you. I wanted to wish you a happy birthday
and to congratulate you on your success of getting the investment,
as well as our marriage, in advance.
Se Yeon!
My friends are here.
I want you to be respectful.
Can you clean this up?
Serve the coffee for us.
Yes.
Sorry.
What?
Thank you.
Thanks to the studd you sent this morning,
Hannamdong Lady decided to help us.
Really?
I'm glad. I'm so glad.
What are you doing?
Is the coffee ready?
It's done.
I'll do it.
Go out.
My friends are gone.
The four of us can have a drink now.
The four of us?
Bring out some dessert.
I thought you'd enjoy it.
Pretending not to know the truth.
Se Yeon.
What do you think, Yoo Jung?
The guy you used to date,
and the guy who's torturing you.
Which one
do you despise more?
Don't answer that.
She has no feeling to me.
When she broke up with me, she told me not to feel guilty of each other.
What? Do you have something to say?
Sorry.
You two look dangerous.
You two look good together.
I think my job here is done. I'll be off.
I'll come back for the plates tomorrow.
So? Don't you like this? This is my gift.
Do you like it?
Do you feel it fun?
I thought you were the one
who did stuff like this for fun.
I told you not to interrupt while I'm talking to Se Yeon.
I think I'll give you my present soon.
Mr. Ahn. You know what?
Those who pretend to be strong are actually nothing.
You look very insecure at the moment.
Thank you for the party.
Get in!
I'll take the bus.
You said you'd listen to me.
Get in.
I know Min Hyuk.
I've known him since kindergarten.
When Seo Ji Hee died,
I thought I could have him.
The way he looked at her
is love.
Thank you for the ride, sir.